

Contacts

+33607869016

France, Lyon 69003

o.kuzkina@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/olga-kuzkina/

https://github.com/KuzkinaOlga

Tech Skills

- HTML/CSS
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- JavaScript
- Git
- Node.js
- React.js
- Redux
- JQuery
- Webpack
- Parcel
- REST API

Soft Skills

- Communicative
- Customer Orientation
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork

Language skills

English: upper-intermediate

French: upper-intermediate

Ukrainian: native

Russian: native

Olga Kuzkina

Full-Stack Developer

Summary

I'm a Full-Stack developer. I got my first experience a year ago and since then I have been steadily reaching the heights in the field of computer technology. I already have experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js and I'm starting to learning Node.js, and of course I continue to delve into the knowledge of all these areas. Since the development of technology does not stand still, my development is also accelerating.

Talented and dependable worker, with extensive communication experience, easily included in a team. Extremely motivated for career change goal. Dedicated Computer Information technology.

Project Experience

WebPage for WebStudio / HTML, SCSS

my own project <u>LINK/GitHub to project</u>

WebPage for IceCream shop / JS, HTML, SCSS

team project <u>LINK/GitHub to project</u>

WebPage for library of movies / JS, HTML, SCSS

team project <u>LINK/GitHub to project</u>

Work Experience

2015 - 2022 - Restoration (France)

worked in the restaurant business, went from start to finish on the evolutionary ladder: assistant cook - bartender - manager - owner of my own restaurant

2008 - 2014 - Casting agency owner (Ukraine)

2006 - 2008 - Casting director (Ukraine)

2004 - 2006 - Casting manager (Ukraine)

Education

2021 - 2022

Pending diploma of Full Stack Developer

IT School GOIT (Kyiv)

2001 - 2006

Bachelor's degree in marketing

Kyiv Institute of Advertising